We are joined by Magic 1023.92.7's Vic Jagger.
She is tapping in for another edition of Vicky Vicky for the record.
What is a song that comes to mind that represents the district?
Oh, of course, the song that everyone goes to.
The butt.
Okay.
If you hear the butt, whenever...
Oh, I'm from D.C.
Oh, and the butt.
So how do you feel about Go-Go?
Because I know folks in D.C. do not play about Go-Go.
I love Go-Go.
I was raised on Go-Go.
It's not going anywhere.
A lot of people would say, oh, you guys are just covering songs.
But the Go-Go songs are better than the original songs most of the time.
For the folks that don't know what Go-Go is,
can you give them some kind of like description of what the style of Go-Go music is that represents D.C.?
Go-Go music, when you think of different places, you know, New Orleans and Go-Go, these are musicians.
These are people who play instruments, you know, and the percussion is where it's at.
When you think of Salt-N-Pepa, who has songs inspired by Go-Go, LL Cool J has songs inspired by Go-Go.
It's just a feel-good music where the talent shines through.
They can take any song, turn it around, turn it into a Go-Go song, and we'll have you two-step in.
And people who are not from D.C. will always say, what is that?
Is that?
That's Go-Go.
And it's just one of those types of music that you feel in your soul.